Guide to the Sergei Germanovich Pushkarev Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Additional Material, 1951-1984; Accession 1991-M-074; 3 linear feet (7 boxes)
  - Manuscripts
    - The Bolshevik Seizure of Power in 1917
      - Text of third (final) version, undated (Box 3, Folder 33-38)
    - The Emergence of Modern Russia
      - Additions and corrections, undated (Box 3, Folder 39)
      - Bibliography, undated (Box 4, Folder 40-43)
      - Changes and additions, undated (Box 4, Folder 44-47)
      - Correspondence and reviews, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 48)
      - Index of persons, undated (Box 4, Folder 49)
      - Notes, undated (Box 4, Folder 50)
      - Preface and epilogue, undated (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - "The History of Russia" (lectures at Fordham University)
      - Typescript, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 52-56)
      - Manuscript, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 57-60)
    - Obzor russkoi istorii: typescript, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 61-66)
    - Rossiia v XIX veke: typescript, undated (Box 6, Folder 67-73)
  - Printed works
    - Reprints, 1931-1974 (Box 7, Folder 74-78)
  - Personal Papers
    - Teaching files
      - Fordham University. Institute of Russian Studies: correspondence, notes and syllabi, 1951-1953 (Box 7, Folder 79)
      - Columbia University
        - Correspondence and lecture notes, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 80)
        - Lecture notes and bibliography, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 81)
      - Birthday celebration: correspondence and printed material, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 82)